const STORE = [
  { 
    question: 'Which is not part of the exposure triangle?',
    choices: [
       'ISO',
       'Focus Meter', 
       'Aperture', 
       'Shutter Speed'
      ],
    answerKey: 1
  }, 
  {
    question: `Which setting adds or reduces motion blur?`,
    choices: [
      'Meter Mode', 
      'Aperture', 
      'Depth of Field', 
      'Shutter Speed'
      ],
      answerKey: 3
  }, 
  {
    question: `What does Aperture control?`,
    choices: [
       `Color Balance`, 
       `Motion Blur`, 
       `Depth of Field`, 
       `Stabilization`
      ],
    answerKey: 2
  }, 
  {
    question: `What does Shutter Speed control?`,
    choices: [
       `Color Balance`, 
       `Motion Blur`, 
       `Depth of Field`, 
       `Stabilization`
      ],
    answerKey: 1
  }, 
  {
    question: `How can you darken an image?`,
    choices: [
      `Raise the Shutter Speed`, 
      `Raise the Aperture`, 
      `Post Lightroom Processing`, 
      `All of the Above`
      ],
    answerKey: 3
  }, 
  {
    question: `What is the typical unit for White Balance?`,
    choices: [
       `Kelvin`, 
       `Celsius`, 
       `Nits`, 
       `Degrees`
      ],
    answerKey: 0
  }, 
  {
    question: `What format allows for the most control in editing?`,
    choices: [
       `JPEG`, 
       `TIFF`, 
       `RAW`, 
       `PNG`
      ],
    answerKey: 2
  }, 
  {
    question: `What does ISO control?`,
    choices: [
       `Sensitivity of the Sensor`, 
       `White Balance`, 
       `Depth of Field`, 
       `All of the Above`
      ],
    answerKey: 0
  }, 
  {
    question: `Which shutter speed is the fastest?`,
    choices: [
       `1/50`, 
       `1/250`, 
       `f2.8`, 
       `f9`
      ],
    answerKey: 1
  }, 
  {
    question: `Which Aperture setting is the widest?`,
    choices: [
       `1/50`, 
       `1/250`, 
       `f2.8`, 
       `f9`
      ],
    answerKey: 3
  }
];